So moving to slide 10, Lectio.
So we had a strong quarter going, 59% driven by strong demand we saw across the globe. In the U.S.,
we were up 55% in quarter two. We outpaced the advanced lipid lowering market. This was driven
by monthly TRX growth of 49%, demonstrating Lectio's differentiated profile, strong
persistency. The demand is being driven with increasing depth in the priority health systems
that we're targeting. The most important segment,
yes, is this segment for us, which is the Medicare Part B segment,
where we see 23.3 percent share. That's up 3.6 percent year to date. And we see an
opportunity for a continued expansion. I think even with orals launching, our opportunity remains
for driving strong growth in the segments that wants infrequently administered physician-administered
medicines for light lipid lowering in the United States. And we see this as an
attractive and growing segment that supports our peak sales potential in the U.S.
the U.S. and beyond. Outside of the U.S., NRDL inclusion is unlocking significant demand.
We saw that in quarter one and continues in quarter two. Our market share has doubled now
versus the pre-NRDL share we were previously seeing. We also see sustained growth in Europe
and Japan, so overall pleased with our performance. We keep generating additional
data for Lectio. Three world studies demonstrated that Inclisir and Lectio improves adherence and
persistence compared to other advanced lipid-lowering therapies. And then we also have
the V-Challenge head-to-head study of Inclisirin versus mempidoic acid, which will prevent N-ESC.
And lastly, we're on track as well for our two outcome studies to read out in 2027 for Lectio.
Then moving to slide 11, Semblix had a very strong quarter, 89% constant
currency growth in the U.S. and in the U.S. and in the U.S. and in the U.S. and in the U.S.
We see growth driven by both U.S. and ex-U.S. performance. In the U.S., we had 93%
growth in the quarter. This is driven by sustained leadership across all lines,
but importantly, we now expect to reach a first-line NBRX leadership share
in the second half of the year. You can see steady improvements in that NBRX share,
a first-line NBRX share. Outside of the U.S., we're primarily still driven by the third line
and beyond performance with 75%.
But importantly, for future growth, we're seeing early-line adoption now starting to pick up.